quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "How many subnets on the following subnet mask 255.128.0.0?",
        "correct_answer": "2",
        "options": ["4", "2", "8", "16"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alan recently implemented an intrusion prevention system designed to block common network attacks from affecting his organization. What type of risk management strategy is Alan pursuing?",
        "correct_answer": "Risk mitigation",
        "options": ["Risk transference", "Risk mitigation", "Risk avoidance", "Risk acceptance"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the IP Header, which Protocol Number identifies ICMP?",
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "options": ["6", "4", "2", "1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the IP Header, which Protocol Number identifies TCP?",
        "correct_answer": "6",
        "options": ["1", "4", "6", "13"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which service uses TCP 2049?",
        "correct_answer": "NFS",
        "options": ["MySQL", "NFS", "Microsoft SQL", "VNC"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the range of “Well-Known” ports?",
        "correct_answer": "0 to 1023",
        "options": ["1024 to 49151", "49152 - 65535", "0 to 1022", "0 to 1023"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many subnets on the following subnet mask 255.255.255.224?",
        "correct_answer": "8",
        "options": ["2", "4", "6", "8"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hosts on the following subnet mask 255.255.255.0?",
        "correct_answer": "254",
        "options": ["253", "255", "254", "128"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hosts are available on the following subnet mask 255.255.255.224?",
        "correct_answer": "30",
        "options": ["30", "32", "64", "62"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the EAL levels provides methodically designed, tested and reviewed?",
        "correct_answer": "EAL4",
        "options": ["EAL2", "EAL4", "EAL3", "EAL7"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the books in the Rainbow Series deals with Trusted Computer Evaluation?",
        "correct_answer": "Orange Book",
        "options": ["Blue book", "Tan Book", "Orange Book", "Green Book"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the books in the Rainbow Series deals with formal verification systems?",
        "correct_answer": "Purple book",
        "options": ["Red book", "Purple book", "Blue book", "Green book"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the requirement of Biba Model?",
        "correct_answer": "No write-up, no read-down",
        "options": ["No write-up, no read-down", "No read-up, no write-down", "No read-up, no write-up", "No read-down, no write-down"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct order of a penetration testing methodology?",
        "correct_answer": "Pre-engagement, intelligence gathering, threat modelling, vulnerability analysis, exploitation, post exploitation and reporting",
        "options": [
            "Pre-engagement, intelligence gathering, threat modelling, vulnerability analysis, exploitation, post exploitation and reporting",
            "Pre-engagement, intelligence gathering, vulnerability analysis, threat modelling, exploitation, post exploitation and reporting",
            "Intelligence gathering, Pre-engagement, threat modelling, vulnerability analysis, exploitation, post exploitation and reporting",
            "Pre-engagement, threat modelling, intelligence gathering, vulnerability analysis, exploitation, post exploitation and reporting"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the statement best describes a passive FTP?",
        "correct_answer": "The client requests the server for the port number prior to establishing connection",
        "options": [
            "The client provides the port number for the server to establish connection",
            "The client requests the server for the port number prior to establishing connection",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which class is the IP address 190.90.80.92 a member of?",
        "correct_answer": "Class B",
        "options": ["Class A", "Class B", "Class C", "Class D"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which layer of the OSI model do routers operate at?",
        "correct_answer": "Layer 3",
        "options": ["Layer 1", "Layer 2", "Layer 3", "Layer 4"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following describes the “Data Controller”?",
        "correct_answer": "The person with the ultimate responsibility for the data",
        "options": [
            "The person's data being processed",
            "A person that processes data on behalf of a data controller",
            "The person with the ultimate responsibility for the data",
            "The system processing the data"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement correctly defines a digital certificate?",
        "correct_answer": "The owner's public key, essential information, signed by a CA using their private key",
        "options": [
            "The owner's private key, essential information, signed by a CA using their private key",
            "The owner's public key, essential information, signed by a CA using their private key",
            "The owner's private key, essential information, signed by a CA using their public key",
            "The owner's private key, essential information, signed by a CA using their public key"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following section of the CMA 1990 deals with facilitating further offences?",
        "correct_answer": "Section 2",
        "options": ["Section 3A", "Section 1", "Section 3", "Section 2"]
    }
]
